Uka's
fun and lovely showroom
Yay!
Hello everyone, we are Uka
We are looking forward to it
I, Koharu Wakana will be the host for
today
Please
We will do our best
Let's introduce ourselves
I'm Serizawa Moa. Nice to meet you.
I'm Muramatsu Rizu. Nice to meet you.
Today is the 207th episode of our
showroom video, so thank you for
watching our funny style showroom!
We everytime receive
Everyone, please get the avatar of
Anuka.
Each avatar is also distributed.
Please get it.
Thank you.
It's time to spread.
To get more people to watch this
broadcast, we will post an announcement
on AX.
Please spread.
Please.
What should we do today?
What should we do?
It's the first time to be in the
showroom.
Yes.
I'm going to ask you a question.
What?
Okay.
What should I do?
Five.
Go.
Everyone is already...
Let's do this.
No, let's do this.
This is 5.
Is this 5?
It's 5.
Shall we start?
Yes.
Start.
But doesn't this look like 5?
It does.
See?
It looks like 5.
If you think it's 5, it's 5.
How about raising your upper hand like
this?
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Thank you.
It's over.
Please put it on the poster.
Thank you.
Yes.
Let's move on to this corner.
It's a fun and fun 15 minute news
report.
We're going to talk freely about the fun
and fun of the past.
Yes.
We're a group that keeps time.
We'll talk about the events of the group
and the events of the individual in 15
minutes.
Yes.
It's going to be over no matter how much
we talk.
I see.
We'll talk about it until then.
Yes.
It's easy.
We'll do our best.
I think so.
We can do it.
It's going to be.
Yes.
Then, ready.
Start.
Yes.
Then, first of all, what should we do in
the group?
That's right.
We went to Fukuoka.
Yes.
We're on the spring tour.
We came to Fukuoka on April 27th.
Yes.
We came.
That's where the Steps' concert started.
The spring tour that we're currently
doing is called Hop! Step Jump.
It's three stages.
That's right.
It's a triple course.
Steps' concert began from Fukuoka's
concert on April 27th.
We did it.
Yes.
I've been to Fukuoka several times.
I have.
It was the first time to go to Fukuoka
with a new system.
Yes.
It was the first time.
I went to Fukuoka for the first time.
Yes.
I went to Fukuoka.
I went to Fukuoka for the first time.
Yes, it's my first time. I went to
Fukuoka for the first time.
How was it?
The atmosphere is different.
There is also a convenience store.
We all ate that.
Tonkotsu ramen was delicious.
It was delicious.
I was able to stay in Fukuoka for a
while.
So I ate a lot of rice at night.
The next day was also delicious.
Koharu was really good at the rice shop.
Why?
It was amazing.
It was probably normal clothes.
Koharu was wearing a white tank top.
It was a white tank top.
It was cold, so I couldn't think of it.
It was interesting.
I was fine.
I was happy to see RINA and her hair.
I was happy too.
I'm also in the video.
I'm in the video.
It was amazing.
I was impressed by RINA.
I thought it was just RINA.
But we were next to each other.
I was two minutes away from RINA.
She repeated the word five minutes ago.
What?
Please apologize.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
I was sitting with RINA.
Koharu's words were very interesting.
I thought it was interesting.
Wait.
I thought you watched it.
RINA kept saying it.
I was caught by her and said it for five
minutes.
I don't remember what it was.
What was it?
I'm curious.
I don't know what it was.
I'm a little...
I forget it quickly.
I want to stop it.
But I just did it.
It was really interesting.
I repeated it.
The member impersonations are quite
common.
It's like doing it in a bar.
It was fun.
Next day too.
Dazai and Tenbang went there together.
We ate a lot.
She gave us a free time.
What did you eat?
I ate Ume-gai mochi.
I ate Ume-gai mochi, which is famous in
the Nether-Storm Man-bun.
I ate a famous fried chicken.
I got a bite.
It was a little funny.
I went to the edge of the room to eat
fried chicken.
I was sitting down.
A pigeon came and I couldn't do it.
I was screaming.
I was a normal reaction.
I was surprised because I was surprised.
I was the most excited.
I was standing in front of the wall.
I looked back and everyone was looking
at me.
I was surprised.
People around me were surprised too.
They said, I was moving.
I was surprised.
I was screaming and shouting.
It was a great day in Fukuoka.
It was fun.
This is the end of the spring tour.
Next is Osaka park tour.
So, come and visit us again next time.
Thank you for watching.
So, there is a song called the title of
our song.
It's a long song.
This song was used for the ending of the
secret ID card.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
The ending of the song will be released
until June, May, June, June, June.
I hope you will watch the ending.
The song called transparent is being
released.
Have you seen it?
I have seen it.
It's been a while since it was released.
I'm sure you've seen it.
I'm on TikTok.
But you haven't seen it in the showroom,
have you?
So, let's see it.
I want to see it.
Let's see it.
Please.
It's so cute
It's so refreshing
It's really refreshing
Oh, that's it.
We played it in the middle of the
chorus.
I think it's a very youthful song just
by looking at the back of the girl.
I think it's a short video that feels
like you're playing a song on the
poolside.
And it's a school uniform, so it feels
like school.
That's right.
I don't think you're on the poolside
anymore.
You don't usually be on the poolside.
I think the uniform is very emotional.
I think the music is very good from the
music sheet.
I think it's good.
Who's the model?
Who?
We're the model.
Everyone, the back of the girl is very
different from ours.
I think I might be the model.
Maybe.
It's a short video.
Everyone, there is a post posted on our
UKKA X.
Did you see it?
If you want to see it, please watch it a
little bit and come back.
It came out! It was posted at 19 o'clock
earlier.
It says tomorrow, September 22nd, on
YouTube.
What is this?
It's a little similar to the short video
of the transparent one.
What will happen tomorrow?
The one that is being released now is
the short version of the transparent
lyric video.
Everyone may be curious.
What is it?
I'm looking forward to it.
I think it would be nice if you could
wait until tomorrow, September 22nd.
Yes, please.
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder what it will be.
You can watch the short version of the
short version from the beginning.
Yes.
You can listen to a lot of transparent
music.
Please wait.
Please.
I don't know what it was, but I want to
talk more from now on.
Yes.
I want to see the dance moves a bit.
Is there such a thing.
That's it.
Let's explain it.
I think this time...
Can you listen to me slowly?
A little distant collapses.
I think I'll listen to this partner
about one moment.
My katana seems to fall into a lot of
different order.
To be honest it is anymore.
I think it's addictive too.
From the Exodus practice or something.
Yes.
Let's hear the checking.
What did we do.
I'm curious about what you did in the
past.
Please tell me.
I went back to my parents' house.
Oh, that's right.
It's a good chance.
I was working.
Thank you for your hard work.
I don't know.
I think I had a lot of time to relax.
I have a lot of work.
I went to the art museum.
You cooked.
What did you cook?
I made a drama at once.
It may be the joy of the day off.
It's like Golden Age.
What is Golden Week?
Can you explain Golden Week?
Golden Week is...
There are many holidays in May.
I don't know when it started, but I
think there were many holidays.
May is a holiday.
There are many days of the month.
Do you know when it started?
The first one.
It's over.
Yesterday was the last day of the
holiday.
Yes.
It started before the first holiday.
That's right.
Did it end?
It's over.
It was a good day.
I see.
It's over.
But there are many UCCA concerts after
Golden Week.
There are many tours.
Kawasaki and Sendai.
I think everyone will enjoy it.
Yes.
There are three concerts every week.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes.
If we do it three times, wait.
Wait, should we finish the Step Coin?
It's over.
Right?
Step Coin will end in May.
What?
Isn't it crazy?
It's so crazy.
What?
Wait, if we finish it once every week,
and do it three more times, it'll be
four.
It's four times.
Crazy.
It's amazing to do it three more times.
It's crazy.
On the contrary.
I see.
And in June.
It's crazy.
Oh, right.
Wow.
It's not there.
It's so fast.
Isn't it crazy?
This month.
It's only now.
I'm sure you'll wear it.
And the costumes are also upgraded.
Yes.
It's only in May that you can see the
costumes of the Step concert.
That's right.
The shape changes.
It's going to be changed.
It's going to change.
Everyone.
Right?
Right.
It's true.
Jump is jump again.
The content and costumes will change.
To the most inspiring , a lot will be
made.
All staff members have never been
Special Group 9 members in preparations
for the concert.
Right.
Who is B Legislative Sukishima?
Go!
I Julian.
Yes, go.
Who is Haruka road, Україards Marian?
Right.
Who is Yon visited to this theme this
time?
It'spero, who did so I think there is a
message.
I'm ready forLab, you are a special
group.
Truly.
I think the theme of the Everyone's
Style will join this.
It's also made.
I'm sorry.
ю
It looks like it well separated.
It person like to come and I think that
they are be fun to come.
Young girl used to was like klein small
print
But It was used to mean she fl webinars
But while Lilly was sing she made it
very join
Strong fl multinites
하세요
Let's go
I was standing there and I was singing
the first and second part of the song.
I was thinking about it and I was
laughing.
I thought I should do it later.
I was confident.
Did you do it intentionally?
I did it before the second chorus.
I thought I should do it too.
I was thinking about it and I thought I
should do it.
I thought I was singing it.
You are amazing.
You were thinking about it.
I was singing it but I was thinking
about it.
It was funny.
After that, I was practicing my voice.
I was thinking about what to do when Rie
and Sorachan were using my head.
I was thinking about it.
I thought Sorachan was going to hit me.
It was a strange reaction.
Both of us were thinking about it.
I was thinking about it.
I wanted to do it with a towel again.
Me too.
I wanted to do it.
I want to do it.
I will run away.
It's possible.
I want to do it.
I think you can only see it in the
steps.
If it's a live performance, it's a
highlight.
It's a feeling of chaos.
I hope you can enjoy it.
I hope so.
Osaka is a group that appeared in the
Maw Loop.
It's a two-day tour, so it's amazing.
Wow!
What did you say?
I thought you were saying something
else.
I didn't say anything.
It's the beginning, so it's over.
But we got the first chance.
I think so.
Yes.
It's over.
That's all for the 15-minute news
report.
Yay!
We talked a lot, didn't we?
Let's move on to the next segment.
Yes.
Fun and fluffy multi-idol!
Multi-idol!
The work of the members of UCCA is
mainly to perform live shows and appear
on TV shows.
We aim to be active in the multi-idol
world.
So today we will predict when various
jobs will come and predict them.
Yes!
It's important!
Is there any job you want to do?
UCCA usually performs live shows and
radio shows.
I wonder what it is.
Rina and Sora are currently working on
acting.
Yes, they are.
What is it?
But if I have to choose, I want to work
as a model.
I want to work hard.
You look like an adult.
Really?
I'll do my best.
Your face is so beautiful, so you look
good.
I used to have a forehead when I was a
new member, but I thought I would look
good too.
I'm wearing a Murahoshi outfit on
Instagram.
Murahoshi clothes?
She's wearing a Murahoshi outfit.
I think it's a good look.
I think it's fashionable to wear Ma-
chan's clothes.
Koharu has a good style.
I want you to separate.
I like the style of recent girls.
I like it too.
I don't like it.
But I like the style.
I don't change much.
You're amazing.
I'm so happy.
I'm wondering how far you've come.
I'm jealous.
Recently, I've been changing my hair
color and nails.
I think Uka has a pure image.
I think it's good for the group, but if
you do your own work,
I think it's a little different.
I want to try caracom.
I'm sure there's a caracom model.
Caracom is on the album today, but I
haven't put it in much, so I'm a little
worried.
There's a caracom model, so I think it's
good to introduce the nails.
Cute.
There's nothing.
It's cute.
I'm a junior high school student.
But Ma-chan is cute.
It's cute.
It's called Magnet.
It's a magnet.
It changes the angle of view depending
on the place.
It's amazing.
It's cute.
It's shiny.
It's summer-like.
It's blue, isn't it?
Yes.
When I dyed my hair, my hair was pink.
The pink shampoo was a little purple
because I did it with my hands.
Does it get colored?
It's colored.
That's why I put it on my hands.
I didn't know that.
Do you have a broken hair?
No.
Finally, you can go home and bring your
favorite play då.
Oh.
I will completely see it.
You have a pool tent?
But you need to wear it.
Weavers wear it the only time they go
out, so you can't just sit there doing
that.
When you fight the current world, you
can't fight that force, right?
That's right.
I also put a song in my music book, so I
thought it was difficult to sing a
simple song.
I think you're playing a difficult song.
I gave it to TAKE.
It was amazing.
It's good.
It's difficult.
I have various dreams.
I would like to talk about various
projects from now on.
First of all, I would like to talk about
the content of the project.
What should I do?
There are four topics, but I would like
to choose one of them and talk about it.
I think the first one is good.
The first is to publish a dictionary.
The title is a dictionary.
It's a dictionary.
It's a dictionary of your life
experiences.
What should I do?
I wrote a sketchbook.
I want to thank you three.
It's a little different, but our lives
are different.
It seems that we have different choices
of words.
Certainly.
So, it's difficult.
I wrote my life on the wall.
My life is different.
I'm done.
It's not over.
I'm done, but I'm not sure.
Wait a minute.
We received a big bear from the D.B. of
Anonis.
Thank you.
Thank you for the big bear.
I don't know if the name of the big bear
is right.
It's a big bear.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
It's a dictionary.
We have exactly the same character.
Exactly.
Write давай or not
I've never written it, but I know what
it is.
What should I do? My eyes are stopped.
It's difficult. What would you do if you
were me?
Please give me a hint.
I want to do something like Koharu's
never-ending story.
I think it's cool.
I want to do something like Koharu's
never-ending story.
I think it's cool if you make me look
cool.
I want to make you look cool.
What would you do if you were me?
I think it's really funny.
I want to do something like Koharu's
never-ending story.
It's cool.
It's cool to have a four-person school
uniform.
That's right.
It's embarrassing to write the title of
Serizawa Moa's everyday cute girl.
When I wrote the title of the book, I
was confused about the response of the
person who gave it to me.
But Moa is cute, so you can read the
person who wants to read the cute girl.
I can't read the person who wants to be
naked.
What should I do?
I think I should say something like,
I want to be with myself.
similar ver.
I'm thinking about it. I'm thinking
about what I want to write.
What is the meaning of the word Ma-chan?
Wait, I'm thinking of the name of the
famous character of SILVERMAN.
I don't like that.
You're thinking of the character who has
too much underwear.
I'm thinking of the character who has
It's like the name of the character who
has too much underwear.
That's good.
I'm thinking of the character who has
too much underwear.
like that, I still want to eat
I'm sorry.
Please wait a moment.
I finished writing.
Who will start?
I will start.
The person who finished the most.
I will show my own line.
I think it's Serizawa Moa's Life is a
Vampire.
Oh!
That's good.
I only remembered this.
There's also a song called Vivaraveda.
I thought so.
There is.
That's right.
My motto is to enjoy life.
So I think this is close.
It's good.
It's like putting your name in it.
That's right.
The impact is important.
It depends on putting your name in it.
That's right.
I wrote down what I thought was a
vampire in my life.
What is it?
I wrote down what I thought was a
vampire in my life.
That's good.
That's right.
I'll go next.
If I publish a dictionary, what is the
title?
Yes.
This is Hikerakata fall.
Not necessary to come from O direito per
sé at all.
Keep it.
But...
I later everlasting in a live Datte
after the across your future must I
entre I ihrer
Sprint is twelve countries without
shaken 마 compatibility is already
magnified at is lean from One's Stance.
I think it's a good title.
It's amazing that you're a traveler.
I want to read it.
It's cool.
I think it's better to put it in
Hirakata City.
I hope it's published.
I can only write this to RIZI.
Thank you.
Let's read the last one.
OK.
Koharu Wakanda's
The day starts.
I see.
What was it?
I said it in the showroom.
My motto is
The day of the deadline starts.
I don't know the meaning of the
deadline.
I can do anything.
The day starts.
That's how important it is.
I can do anything from now on.
I thought I wouldn't make it to the end.
I'll give you some advice.
You're the only one who can do it.
Moa is using her motto.
I'll do my best to publish this.
I'll change my name.
That's it.
What's the next topic?
I'm going to release a product that I
collaborated with.
What's the product name?
It's good.
I usually use convenience stores.
It's a dream to be able to release a
collaboration product.
What do you want to release?
The product name of the product is also
a dream.
What should I do?
It's already decided.
I think it's me
I decided
I think I'm the only one
I'm the only one
We are
Oh no
I think you all know who I am
I'm curious about the name
Fuku?
What
What do you think?
That's Koharu Chocolate.
I wrote something wrong.
It's okay.
I'm just guessing.
I'll check it out.
I don't know.
It's hard.
I think it would be better to wink at
this time.
I agree.
I think it's better to wink.
I love you
I love you too
Why?
I don't know
I love you
I love you too
It's a long story
Can I call you now?
Yes, you can.
I'll give you the name and the item.
I've decided.
I think I'll be fine.
I like it. I like Koharu's egg bolo.
Oh, I should have chosen the egg bolo.
I like it. It looks like an egg bolo.
What should I do?
I should have chosen the egg bolo.
I miss Riju's Rejuice.
What is it?
It's been 8 years since we started this.
When we were in middle school, we often
had a self-introduction event with
idols.
We were like, please say it together.
We had that.
When I said, everyone,
there was a time when we were like,
Rejuice.
That was the time.
I was like, let's do it.
But it ended 2 or 3 times.
That's fast.
What about you?
I don't have one.
But it ended before you.
So I don't think I had one for a year.
I didn't have one until I joined.
You didn't have one?
That's fast.
Maybe I can hear it.
Maybe it's wrong.
Did you decide?
Go ahead.
Can I start?
Sure.
What do you want to sell?
Ta-da.
Miso soup.
You like miso soup.
I often drink cup miso soup at the
convenience store.
I think that's good.
Nice.
And...
Let's see the product name.
This is Serizawa Moa's face-shrinkable
miso soup.
It's important.
I drink it even if my face is swollen.
But if my face is not swollen, it's
better.
So I drink it on the day of shooting.
I aim to be like model and photographer.
I like it.
I'm happy to hear that.
The important thing is that your face is
not swollen.
I want to drink it.
I want to drink it too.
I think everyone expected miso soup.
I like it.
Which one do you like?
I'll try it.
Is it okay?
Ready?
Haru's head popcorn.
You said it at the end.
I didn't know it at the end.
It's normal.
I thought it was normal.
What kind of product is it?
I often eat popcorn these days.
I always buy a huge popcorn at the
convenience store.
Everyone picks it up.
Popcorn is popular these days, so I
bought it.
It's good.
If you don't do it properly, it's okay
to get angry.
You are not eating popcorn.
It's delicious.
It's delicious and my head is like a
popcorn.
Because it's the first time.
I want you to do it.
There is a person who eats popcorn next
to the product.
I want you to do this.
Certainly.
Like this.
It's interesting.
I want to try it.
It's good.
It was very interesting.
It was interesting.
It was really good to eat vegetables.
It's a good idea.
Please.
I will go to the last.
I will release a convenience store
product that I collaborated with.
The product name is
It's a melon bread that I accidentally
got.
It's cute.
Great.
I drew a picture of this.
I can draw a picture of myself.
When I say,
This is our logo.
That's right.
It's transparent.
Great.
When I saw it, I thought it was a pink
color.
I was wondering what to do with the
contents, but it's a strawberry flavor.
It's cute.
I thought it was pink.
It's pink.
I like melon bread.
If I can collaborate with melon bread, I
don't think so.
It's really cute this year.
It's really cute.
The logo of the product is
I drew it in a good way.
It's cute.
It's nice.
It's good.
I hope we can make it.
I hope so too.
I want to make it into a product.
That's right.
We can come up with many ideas.
That's all for today.
We were the fun and fun multi-idols.
Thank you.
We will come back with the next topic.
The next topic is the fun and fun
mother's day.
It's almost time.
It's 12th of May.
Is it?
It's almost time.
It's this week.
It's the mother's day.
We will be the mother of the day.
Please leave a comment.
Please ask any question.
We will be the mother.
We will wrap up the questions with the
mother's day.
When I clap my hands, we will be the
mother.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Wait.
Can I act like my mother?
My mother is my mother.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
You can act like your mother.
Okay.
Ready?
One, two, three.
I think you are holding it.
It's started.
What's up, everyone?
I bought croquettes for free today.
Hurry up and take a bath, everyone!
Take a bath.
Mom, I'm going to go in first.
What's up, everyone?
Why is your head popcorn?
Well...
Mom, you laugh a lot.
Mom laughs a lot.
Well...
What was it?
Why do you think your head is popcorn?
I asked her.
When I say my head pops, it's popcorn,
right?
Popcorn.
When I say popcorn, it pops, right?
It's because it's your head.
Let's end it.
I can't talk anymore.
It's okay.
Let's go to the next question.
Okay.
Something is cute.
Please wake me up at 6am tomorrow.
I told my mom.
What?
I told my mom to wake me up.
I can't do it alone.
I have to wake up because it's my job.
I woke up.
I did my best.
I'm a devil.
If you tell your mom to wake me up, you
can do it.
I told my mom to wake me up.
I see.
I'm sorry, everyone. I didn't say much.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, it's about time.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Uka's Yuka's Fufuna Showroom 207th
episode.
Ending in a flash.
It's a big one.
Sorry, I answered from the second
question.
Sorry.
I didn't say anything.
Let's go to the announcement.
Please say the word.
I can't think of the word.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
The Journey Begin Tour 2024 Spring Pop
Step Jump is on.
The next show is
May 12th, Sunday
Osaka Banana Hall
The next is
May 19th, Sunday
Kanagawa Spelnova
The next is
May 26th, Sunday
Sendai Darwin
That's right.
The Steps are over at these three parks.
If you haven't planned to go yet, please
go.
Please.
Jump Park is on Saturday, June 22nd,
Kanagawa Yokohama B4.
The last show is
July 7th, Sunday
Tokyo Panda Square Hall.
It's the last tour final.
Tickets are on sale, so please come and
play.
Thank you.
Next.
May 11th, Saturday
I will be on the show at Mawa Loop Osaka
2024.
I will be a big cat.
The time of the show is 12 hours and 45
minutes to 13 hours and 25 minutes.
The special show will be held here, so
please come and play.
It will be the day before the spring
tour.
Let's spend two days together.
Thank you.
Thank you, girl.
And on Saturday, June 15, we will be
performing at the Yatsui Festival 2024.
Thank you!
Please come and see us.
And on the 5th and 6th, on Thursday,
we will be performing at the Showroom
program, Kyan Kyan Room.
The live stream starts at 8pm, so please
watch it.
Please watch it.
That's all.
Now, let's see the final ranking.
We'll start with the 5th place.
5th place, Ebinago.
Thank you.
4th place.
4th place, MOGA.
Thank you.
3rd place, SOUTH TIME.
2nd place, NIA.
Thank you.
1st place, ADONISNO.
Next live broadcast will be on 22nd May.
From 19th of Wednesday.
We will announce the members as soon as
possible.
Please press the heart mark to not miss
the live broadcast.
Please check the individual live
broadcast.
Please.
That's all for the fun and fun show room
of WUKKA.
That's all.
This was WUKKA.
Thank you.
Bye bye.